Finding Aid for the Verley Archer Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Box Listing
  - Series I: Subject Files
    - Klauber, Mrs. George Thomas (Leith Speiden) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Koite, Mrs. John K. (Diana Sloane Field) (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Laughton, Mrs. Anthony (Barbara Clare Bosanquet) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence, Adele (see Auchincloss, Mrs. Louis, Box 1, File 6) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence, Mrs. Blake (Sheila Burden) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Lawrence, Susan (see Winchester, Mrs. John, Box 13, File 20) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - LeBoutillier, John (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - LeBoutillier, Pamela (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - LeBoutillier, Mrs. Thomas (Pamela Tower) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lehman, Mrs. Orin (Wendy Vanderbilt) (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Liddle, George Robert (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Liddle, Mrs. George Roy (Anne Elise Schieffelin) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Liddle, John Jay (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Liddle, Marshall Bayard (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Liddle, Susan Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Livingston, John Morgan (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Loebs, Mrs. Richard G. (Edith Safe) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Long, Jean N. (see Ketcham, Mrs. William T., Box 6, File 33)) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lowman, Mrs. Lawrence (Cathleen Vanderbilt) (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Lutz, Mrs. Pierre (Nancy M. Whitney) (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Mackay, James Jonathan Thorn (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Mackay, Kenneth Peter Lyle (Viscount of Glenapp) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mackay, Lucinda Louise (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mactaggert, Mrs. Sandy A. (Cecile Mary Erickson) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Marckwald, Mrs. Albert H., III (Gertrude F. Kissel) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Marlor, Charles (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Marlor, Mrs. Henry S. (Mildred Ward) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Marlor, Henry S., Jr. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Marlor, James (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Marlor, Linda (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Mauran, Mrs. Duncan Hunter (Louise K. S. Safe) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Mauran, Hope (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Mauran, Louise Safe (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - McCain, Charles S., III (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - McCain, Claudia V. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - McCain, H. Davis (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - McClellan, Mrs. John (Rosalind Brown) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - McClenahan, Barbara Leith (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - McClenahan, Douglas S. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - McClenahan, Lorna (see Anderson, Mrs. Lorna, Box 1, File 2) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - McClenahan, Richard Lee, III (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - McConnell, Mrs. Neil (Serena Mary Churchill Russell) (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - McConnell, Electra Bostwick (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - McDowell, Mrs. Fletcher H. (Electra Bostwick) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - McDowell, Laura (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - McDowell, Linn (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - McMurtry, Mrs. George G. (Teresa Fabbri) (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Meades, Mrs. Harry (Gertrude Webb) (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Meades, Jamie (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Meades, Michael Henry (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Miller, Flora (see Irving, Mrs. Michael, Box 6, File 17) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Miller, Maria- Flora (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Miller, Mrs. George Macculloch (Flora Whitney) (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Miller, Leverett Saltonstall (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Miller, Mrs. Paul L. (Adele Olyphant) (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Miller, Paul Lukens, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Milliken, Christopher C. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Milliken, Mrs. Minot K. (Edith F. Clark) (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Milliken, Minot K., Jr. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Mills, Alice Louise (see Cunningham, Mrs. Thomas D., Jr., Box 3, File 37) (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Mills, Bradford Alan (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Mills, Bradford (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Mills, Mrs. Dudley H. (Louise Morris) (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Mills, Elizabeth Lee (see Hardie, Mrs. James, Box 5, File 13) (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Mills, Gordon Lawrence (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Mills, Harriet L. (see Petty, Mrs. John, Box 9, File 40) (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Minton, Mrs. Tyree (Gail Rockwell) (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Montgomery, Mrs. Horace C. (Margery L. Osborn) (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Morgan, Alida (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Moore, Valerie (see Shields, Mrs. James, Box 10, File 36) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Mrs. Edward P. (Katharine B. Sohier) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Pamela (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Morris, Alice V. (see Sturges, Mrs. Walter, Box 11, File 3) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Morris, Dave Hennen, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Morris, Dave Hennen, III (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Morris, Emily Hammond (see Hadley, Mrs. Hamilton, Box 5, File 4) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Morris, Lawrence (and Mrs. Ruth Lawrence) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Morris, Louise (see Mills, Mrs. Dudley, Box 8, File 40) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Morris, Marian (see Borgfeldt, Mrs. Merton, Box 1, File 26) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Morris, Ralph Noel (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Morris, Susan Bliss (see Carter, Mrs. Fred, Box 2, File 31) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Mott-Trille, Mrs. Frank (Deborah Lucy Bosanquet) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Muir, Mrs. Robert (Rosemary Spencer-Churchhill) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Murphy, Mrs. Robert J. (Cynthia Lyon Finch-Hatton) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Newburg, Mrs. Andre W. G. (Ellen F. Vanderbilt) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Nordberg, Mrs. E. Wayne (Olivia L. Schieffelin) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Nuland, Mrs. James G., Jr. (Hope S. Safe) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Olyphant, Adele (see Miller, Mrs. Paul, Box 8, File 33) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Olyphant, Bevan (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Olyphant, David (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Osborn, Anne Mary (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Osborn, Alice Dodge (see, Brown, Mrs. Newell, Box 1, File 42) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Osborn, Barbara D.(see David, Mrs. George A.L., Box 4, File 9) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Osborn, Charles (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Osborn, Cynthia (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Osborn, Cynthia Sloan (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Osborn, Earl Dodge (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Osborn, Mrs. Frederick H. (Margaret L. Schieffelin) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Osborn, Frederick Henry, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Osborn, Frederick Henry, III (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Osborn, James Duane Pell (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Osborn, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Osborn, Dr. John Jay (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Osborn, John Jay, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Osborn, Maria LaGrange (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Osborn, Margery L. (see Montgomery, Mrs. Horace, Box 8, File 43) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Osborn, Oliver Strong (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Osborn, William Church (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Osborn, Virginia S. (see Earle, Mrs. Morris, Box 4, File 29) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Paine, Helen E. (see Keith, Mrs. Jonathan, Box 6, File 24) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Pate, Mrs. Wallace F. (Lucille M. Vanderbilt) (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Payson, Mrs. Charles S. (Joan Whitney-not a descendant) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Pease, Alice T. (see Roe, Mrs. Thomas, Box 10, File 6) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Pease, Carolyn (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Pease, Derrick A. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Pease, Nicola (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Pease, Richard Peter (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Pease, Sir Richard Thorn (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Pease, Rosalind J. (see Hanbury, Mrs. Evan R., Box 5, File 11) (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Perkins, Mrs. Francis, Jr. (Edith Bradley) (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Perlberg, Mrs. Edward B. (Hope Brown) (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Peterson, Mrs. A. Talbot (Gladys Szechenyi) (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Petty, Mrs. John R. (Harriet Lee Mills) (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Phillips, Mrs. David Gee (Mary O. Webb) (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Porter, Mrs. George, Jr. (Sally Ann Schieffelin) (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Porter, Mrs. William S. (Susan D. Webb) (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Post, Margery L. (see Bruguire, Mrs. Louis, Box 2, File 3) (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Powell, Mrs. Arthur G. (Barbara Jay Schieffelin) (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Pulitzer, Ralph, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Pulitzer, Seward Webb (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Rand, John F. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Rand, Laura M. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Robe, Mrs. Robert S. (Lucy B. Barry) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Cornelia Carter (see Coudenhove-Kalgeri, Countess Hans (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Heinrich, Box 3, File 31) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Gladys (see Thomas, Mrs. Landon, Box 11, File 12) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Eugene Bowie (widower of Cornelia Szechenyi) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Eugene Bowie, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Rockwell, Gail (see Minton, Mrs. Tyree, Box 8, File 42) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Rockwell, Lynn (see Salgo, Mrs. Harvey, Box 10, File 12) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Roe, Mrs. Thomas (Alice Thorn Pease) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Rossen, Mrs. Roger (Katherine Mary Bosanquet) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Roubanis, Mrs. Theodor (Sarah Consuelo Spenser-Churchill) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Russell, Alexandra Brenda (see Birch, Mrs. Timothy, Box 1, File 24) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Russell, Jacqueline (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Russell, Serena Mary Spenser-Churchill (see McConnell, Mrs. Neil, Box 8, File 21) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Safe, Edith (see Loebs, Mrs. Richard, Box 7, File 33) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Safe, Edith (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Safe, Elizabeth (see Bitting, Mrs. Jonathan, Box 1, File 25) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Safe, Hope (see Nuland, Mrs. James, Jr., Box 9, File 12) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Safe, Kenneth Shaw, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Safe, Louise (see Mauran, Mrs. Duncan, Box 8, File 11) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Salgo, Mrs. Harvey (Lynn Rockwell) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Schachter, Mrs. Stanley (Sophia Duckworth) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Schieffelin, Anne Elise (see Liddle, Mrs. George, Box 7, File 28) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Schieffelin, Anne Louise (see Bradley, Mrs. Cameron, Box 1, File 30) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Schieffelin, Barbara (see Bosanquet, Mrs. Charles, Box 1, File 27) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Schieffelin, Barbara J. (see Powell, Mrs. Arthur, Box 9, File 44) (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Schieffelin, Bayard (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Schieffelin, Edward Loomis (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Schieffelin, Eleanor Jay (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Schieffelin, Mrs. Elizabeth (divorced from Elliott F. Schieffelin) (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Schieffelin, Elliott (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Schieffelin, Henry (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Schieffelin, Hope W. (see Dooley, Mrs. John, Box 4, File 22) (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Schieffelin, James Ross (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Schieffelin, John Jay (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Schieffelin, John Jay, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Schieffelin, Joseph Beggs (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Schieffelin, Margaret L. (see Osborn, Mrs. Frederick, Box 9, File 20) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Schieffelin, Mary Jay (see Brown, Mrs. Charles, Box 1, File 37) (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Schieffelin, Nancy J. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Schieffelin, Olivia (see Nordberg, Mrs. E. Wayne, Box 9, File 11) (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Schieffelin, Peter J. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Schieffelin, Sally Ann (see Porter, Mrs. George, Jr., Box 9, File 42) (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Schieffelin, William Jay, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Schieffelin, William Jay, III (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Scribner, Blair Sunderland (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Scribner, Mrs. Charles, Jr. (Dorothy Jean Sunderland) (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Scribner, Charles, III (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Scribner, John (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Secor, Elizabeth (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Secor, Nicholas Tower (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Secor, Susan (see Humes, Mrs. Portner, Jr., Box 6, File 5) (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Secor, Timothy (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Seherr-Thoss, Mrs. Henry W. (Consuelo Vanderbilt Hutton) (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Shepard, Edith (see Fabbri, Mrs. Ernesto, Box 4, File 41) (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Shields, Mrs. James G. (Valerie Moore) (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Shrady, Henry M. II (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Sloane, Emily Vanderbilt (see Hammond, Mrs. John Henry, Box 5, File 8) (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Iris A. (see Christ, Mrs. Donald, Box 3, File 11) (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Virginia (see Hutton, Mrs. William, Box 6, File 13) (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Sohier, Elaine Denegre (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Sohier, Katharine Sage (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Sohier, Katherine Burden (see Morgan, Mrs. Edward, Box 9, File 1) (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Speiden Leith (see Klauber, Mrs. George, Box 7, File 19) (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Spencer, Mrs. Richard (Alice Osborn Brown) (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Starr, Dilwyn T. (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Starr, Francis A. (see Todd, Mrs. John, II, Box 11, File 13) (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Starr, Mrs. Louis (Abbey T. Kissel) (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Stevens, Grace B. (see Sutton, Mrs. Edmond, Box 11, File 6) (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Stevens, Robert L. (widower of Grace Vanderbilt) (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Stokowski, Christopher C. (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Stokowski, Leopold Stanislanovicz (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Stur, Mrs. Louis (Gail Whitney) (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Sturges, David Morris (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Sturges, Lawrence Morris (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Sturges, Margaret Louisa (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Sturges, Marie Hayes (see Houston, Mrs. Frederick, Box 5, File 44) (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Sturges, Peter C. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Sturges, Thomas Rush (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Sturges, Mrs. Walter Knight (Alice V. Morris) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Sturges, Mrs. Edwin S.S. (Dorothy Kissel) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sturges, Rev. Edwin S.S., Jr. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Sunderland, Dorothy J. (see Scribner, Mrs. Charles, Jr., Box 10, File 29) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Sutton, Mrs. Edmond H. (Grace Bayard Stevens) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Szapary, Countess Anthony (Sylvia Szechenyi) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Szapary, Gladys Vanderbilt (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Szapary, Paul Leslie (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Szechenyi, Alice (see Hadik, Countess Bela, Box 5, File 1) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Szechenyi, Gladys (see Peterson, Mrs. A. Talbot, Box 9, File 39) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Szechenyi, Nadine (see Eltz, Mrs. Alexander, Box 4, File 34) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Szechenyi, Sylvia (see Szapary, Countess Anthony, Box 11, File 7) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Tetrault, Mrs. Jacques (Hope Canfield) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Thacher, Mrs. Thomas Day, II (Frances Fell Tower) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Thomas Mrs. Landon, Jr. (Gladys Roberts) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Todd, Mrs. John R., II (Frances A. Starr) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Tower, Alexandra C. (see Hornblower, Mrs. Jonathan, Box 5, File 43) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Tower, Frances (see Thacher, Mrs. John, II, Box 11, File 11) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Tower, Harry Payne (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Tower, Pamela (see LeBoutillier, Mrs. Thomas, Box 7, File 25) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Tower, Roderick (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Tower, Whitney (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Tower, Whitney, Jr. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Twombly, Florence Vanderbilt (see Burden, Mrs. William A.M., Box 2, File 18) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Vanderbilt, Alfred Gwynne, II (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Vanderbilt, Alfred Gwynne, Jr. (the 3rd of this name) (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Vanderbilt, Alice C. (see Hartwell, Mrs. Samuel, Jr., Box 5, File 23) (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Vanderbilt, Mrs. Anne (Colby) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Barbara (see Headley, Mrs. George, Box 5, File 28) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Cathleen (see Lowman, Mrs. Lawrence, Box 7, File 34) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Consuelo (see Balsan, Mrs. Jacques, Box 1, File 14) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Consuelo (see Earl, Mrs. N. Clarkson, Box 4, File 27) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelia S. (see Bulkelley-Johnson, Mrs. John, Box 2, File 4) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelia (see Heddens, Mrs. Kimber J., Box 5, File 29) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelius (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, IV (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Vanderbilt, Ellen (see Newburg, Mrs. Andre, Box 9, File 10) (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Vanderbilt, Emily (see Wade, Mrs. Jeptha, Box 12, File 11) (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Vanderbilt, Emily Thorn (see White, Mrs. Henry, Box 13, File 2) (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Vanderbilt, Frederick W. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Vanderbilt, Mrs. George, III (Louise Mitchell) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Vanderbilt, Gloria Laura Morgan (see Cooper, Mrs. Wyatt, Box 3, File 29) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Vanderbilt, Harold Stirling (and Mrs. Gertrude Conaway Vanderbilt) (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Vanderbilt, Heidi Murray (see Harris, Mrs. Jones, Box 5, File 15) (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Vanderbilt, Lucille M. (see Pate, Mrs. Wallace, Box 9, File 30) (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Vanderbilt, Michael Daggett (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Vanderbilt, Muriel (see Adams, Mrs. John, Box 1, File 1) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Vanderbilt, Nicholas Harvey (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt, Victoria Emerson (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Vanderbilt, Wendy (see Lehman, Mrs. Orin, Box 7, File 26) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Vanderbilt, William Henry (File 1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Vanderbilt, William Henry (File 2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Vanderbilt, William Henry (File 3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Vanderbilt, William Henry, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbilt, William Kitman (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Van Ingen, Herbert P. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Van Ingen, Serena Vanderbilt (see Costin, Mrs. Brackenridge, Box 3, File 30) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Von Heinlein, William Vanderbilt (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Wade, Mrs. Jeptha H. (Emily Vanderbilt) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Wade, William Garretson (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Walken, Bradford H. (stepson of James A. Burden) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Walken, David H. (stepson of James A. Burden) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Wallace, Anna Marie (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Ward, Alexander (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Ward, Mildred (see Marlor, Mrs. Henry, Box 8, File 7) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Ward, Vanderbilt B. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Ward, Wendy (see Wise, Mrs. Henry, Box 13, File 21) (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Waterhouse, Mrs. Charles (Lady Caroline Spenser-Churchill) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Webb, Alex S. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Webb, Angela (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Webb, Barbara (see Henry, Mrs. Barbara, Box 5, File 30) (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Webb, Derick O. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Webb, Derick Vanderbilt (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Webb, Dundeen (see Galbadoni, Mrs. Stephen, Box 4, File 49) (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Webb, Edward Wheeler (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Webb, Electra (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Webb, Electra (see Bostwick, Mrs. Dunbar W. Box 1, File 29) (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Webb, Eliza (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Webb, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Webb, Frederika V. (see Gamble, Mrs. David S., Box 4, File 50) (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Webb, Gertrude (see Meades, Mrs. Harry, Box 8, File 27) (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Webb, Harry (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Webb, Holly (see Darling, Mrs. Michael, Box 4, File 5) (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Webb, Jacob Louis (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Webb, James Watson, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Webb, Kate (see Harris, Mrs. George, Box 5, File 14) (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Webb, Lila Vanderbilt (see Wilmerding, Mrs. John, Box 13, File 18) (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Webb, Laura Havemeyer (see Brown, Mrs. Archibald M., Box 1, File 36) (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Webb, Marshall C. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Webb, Mary O. (see Phillips, Mrs. David, Box 9, File 41) (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Webb, Richard Humphrey (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Webb, Robert M. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Webb, Samuel Blatchley (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Webb, Samuel Blatchley, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Webb, Samuel Watson (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Webb, Susan D. (see Porter, Mrs. William, Box 9, File 43) (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Webb, Mrs. Vanderbilt (widow of Vanderbilt H. Webb) (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Webb, William Gaynor (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Webb, William Osborn (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Webb, Mrs. William Seward, II (widow of William Seward Webb, II) (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Webb, William Seward, III (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Webb, William Seward, IV (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Weisman, Mrs. Robert (Rachel Goodman) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - White, Mrs. Henry (Emily Thorn Vanderbilt) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Whitney, C. Scollay (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Whitney, C. Searle (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt (File 1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt (File 2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Whitney, Flora (see Miller, Mrs. George, Box 8, File 31) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Whitney, Gail (see Stur, Mrs. Louis, Box 10, File 46) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Whitney, Gifford C. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Whitney, Harry Payne, II (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Whitney, Heather (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Whitney, Joan (see Payson, Mrs. Charles, Box 9, File 31) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Whitney, John Hay (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Whitney, Nancy (see Lutz, Mrs. Pierre, Box 7, File 35) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Whitney, Nancy M. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Wilde, Alice L. (see Field, Mrs. Michael, Box 4, File 45) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Wilde, G. William (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Wilde, Mrs. H. George (Marjorie Lila Field) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Wilde, Lila Sloan (see Berle, Mrs. Peter A.A., Box 1, File 21) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Wilde, Mary Kileen (see Carswell, Mrs. Robert, Box 2, File 28) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Wilde, Nancy M. (see Hahn, Mrs. Henry, Box 5, File 5) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Wilde, Peter Osgood (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Wilde, Peter Osgood, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Wilde, Victoria Jean (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Wilmerding, James W. W. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Wilmerding, Mrs. John Currie (Lila Vanderbilt Webb) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Wilmerding, John Currie, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Wilmerding, Lila (see Kirkland, Mrs. David, Box 7, File 9) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Winchester, Mrs. John F. (Susan Lawrence) (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Wise, Mrs. Henry A. III (Wendy Ward) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Wood, Mrs. L. Phillips (Elliot Bostwick) (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Wood, Michael Dunbar (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Wood, Treva (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Catharine Juliette Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Emily Elvira Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Ethelinda Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Maria Louise Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mary Alicia Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Phoebe Jane Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Sophia Johnson Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - William Henry Vanderbilt Branch (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Childless Children of Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Series II: Vanderbilt University Centennial
    - Vanderbilt Family Questionnaires, A-C (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Vanderbilt Family Questionnaires, D-J (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt Family Questionnaires, K-M (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Vanderbilt Family Questionnaires, N-S (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Vanderbilt Family Questionnaires, T-W (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Address Lists Prepared for William H. Vanderbilt (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Form Letters Sent to Vanderbilt Family Members (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Publicity and Articles about the Vanderbilt Centennial (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Project Administration (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Responses to William H. Vanderbilt, re: Reunion (1 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Responses to William H. Vanderbilt, re: Reunion (2 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Responses to William H. Vanderbilt, re: Reunion (3 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Responses to William H. Vanderbilt, re: Reunion (4 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 13)